export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: 'How does Nelson Mandela define the meaning of courage?',
    choices: [
      'Triumph over fear',
      'Triumph over love',
      'Triumph over selfish',
      'Triumph over poverty',
    ],
    answer: 'Triumph over fear',
  },
  {
    question: 'Where did ceremonies take place?',
    choices: [
      'Rockstone amphitheater',
      'Sandstone ampitheater',
      'Glass stone ampitheater',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'Sandstone ampitheater',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which flame can be hidden but never extinguished?',
    choices: [
      "Man's love",
      "Man's natural way",
      "Man's goodness",
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: "Man's goodness",
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which day was the largest gathering of international leaders on South African soil for the installation of South Africa’s first democratic, non-racial government?',
    choices: ['9th May', '10th May', '11th May', '12th May'],
    answer: '10th May',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a country’s greatest wealth?',
    choices: [
      'Its minerals',
      'Its people',
      'Its technology',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'Its people',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does depths of opperession create?',
    choices: [
      'oppressed',
      'heights of character',
      'poverty',
      'lack of freedom',
    ],
    answer: 'heights of character',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who, according to Mandela is not free?',
    choices: ['oppressor', 'oprressed', 'both 1 and 2', 'none of the above'],
    answer: 'item1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which party did Mandela join?',
    choices: [
      'Indian National Congress',
      'African National Congress',
      'National African Party',
      'he did not join any party',
    ],
    answer: 'African National Congress',
  },
  {
    question: 'What realisations did Mandela have of his boyhood freedom?',
    choices: [
      'it is just an illusion',
      'it is the triumph over fear',
      'both 1 and 2',
      'none  of the  above',
    ],
    answer: 'it is the triumph over fear',
  },
  {
    question: 'Why were two National Anthems sung?',
    choices: [
      'to imply unity',
      'to mark the end of racial discrimination',
      'to mark the end of gender discrimination',
      'Both 1 and 2',
    ],
    answer: 'Both 1 and 2',
  },
];
